(Howard:)Were you quoting someone
or is it tattooed on the small of your back?
(Raj:)I was quoting a man who knows a thing
or two about women: Sir Elton John.
(Leonard:)So did you love it? Of course you
loved it. Tell me how much you loved it.
(Penny:)It was cute.
Aw, don't say "cute." That's the worst.
- What's wrong with cute?
- It just makes things seem small.
(Leonard:)It diminishes them.
(Penny:)So you want me to stop calling
your little tushy cute?
(Leonard:)You can try,
but nobody's gonna believe you.
(Leonard:)I don't understand how you can watch
a show that great and not be excited by it.
- I liked it. I'm excited.
- Well, then tell your face.
- What do you want from me?
- You know what? Never mind.
(Leonard:)We gave it a shot.
Let's just see what else is on.
(Penny:)Oh, come on, don't be like that.
I'm sorry I called it cute.